buildingconnected.com 2019-09-20

# Privacy Policy

Welcome to BuildingConnected.com (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes how BuildingConnected, Inc. ("we", "us" and "our") collects, handles and uses personal information collected from users or visitor to the Site and its services. By using the Site or services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy.

## What personal information do we collect? 

"Personal information" is information that identifies (whether directly or indirectly) a particular individual, such as the individual's name, postal address, email address and telephone number. We collect the following personal information from users that register to use the Services on the Site: first and last name, email address, postal or physical address, phone or other contact information, occupation, industry, education, licenses, work experience, employment, and qualifications

We may also collect such personal information when users access certain documents or services on the Site, when users submit Request for Proposals or responses thereto using our Site, when users respond to surveys, when users participate in contests, sweepstakes and other marketing promotions and when users send an inquiry or other communication to us.

The submission of personal information is voluntary. However, you may not be able to access certain services or features on our Site unless register and provide such personal information. We may use the personal information we collect in the following ways relating to our business:

  * to develop, enhance, market sell or otherwise provide information, products or services;
  * to process purchases or other transactions through the Site;
  * to contact and respond to any communications from users;
  * to conduct or administer contests, sweepstakes or other promotions in which you have participated;
  * to customize the user's experience or homepage on the Site; and
  * to develop and manage our business and operations.

We may also use such personal information to enforce the Terms and Condition for use of the Site or this Privacy Policy, to detect and protect us and other third parties against error, negligence, breach of contract, fraud, theft and other illegal activity, to comply with any legal or regulatory requirements or provisions; or for any other purpose to which a user might consent.

We may also track non-personal information about web pages and content accessed by visitors (see Cookies below) to the Site and the number of times such content is accessed by a specific user. We may collect this non-personal information to improve the quality of the Site and the products and services offered through the Site

## To whom do we disclose personal information?

Since BuildingConnection.com is a social networking site, there are aspects of the Site that are available to be viewed by others or by the general public. For example, you may be permitted to create a profile page on the Site. You agree that any personal information you provide to BuildingConnected for this purpose may be made publicly available as part of your BuildingConnected profile.

We may also disclose personal information in the following other situations:

  * We may disclose personal information to third parties (e.g., data storage and processing facilities) that we use to assist us in providing our services, subject to similar obligations of confidentiality to those contained in this Policy;
  * We may disclose personal information where you have specifically authorized us to do so in connection with registering at our Site or in some other written communication;
  * We may disclose personal information if required by law, court and administrative agency order, subpoena or other legal action or by law enforcement;
  * We may disclose person information if it is found that your use of the Site violates our Terms and Conditions, policies, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by BuildingConnected to protect BuildingConnected's legal rights and/or property or the rights and/or property of third parties; and
  * Finally, we may disclose personal information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of our stock or assets in the line of business that this Policy relates or upon any other corporate reorganization.

Except as noted above, BuildingConnected does not sell, rent or transmit personal information to other organizations.

We may also share aggregate demographic, statistical and other information regarding use of our Site, products and services, with third parties for marketing and other purposes, but such aggregate information will not specifically identify any particular user.

## BuildingConnected Discussion Forums and Chat Rooms

If you participate in a BuildingConnected blog, discussion forum or chat room, you should be aware that the information you provide there will be made broadly available to others, who have access to that blog, discussion forum or chat room. Also, please recognize that individual blogs, forums and chat rooms may have additional rules and conditions. Each participant's opinion on a blog, forum or chat room is his or her own and should not be considered as reflecting the opinion of BuildingConnected.

## Linked Sites

The Site may, from time to time, provide links to other third party websites ("Linked Sites") which are outside our control and not covered by this Policy and may have privacy policies that are different from this Policy. BuildingConnected is not responsible for the acts or omissions of any Linked Site. You are encouraged to review the privacy policies posted on all Linked Sites before using them or providing them personal information.

## Children

Our Site and Services do not and will not target and are not intended to solicit or attract children. BuildingConnected does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information. For the purposes of this Policy, children means anyone under the age of 13.

## Use of Suppliers

In some cases BuildingConnected uses suppliers to collect, use, analyze and otherwise process information on its behalf. It is BuildingConnected's practice to require such suppliers to handle information in a manner consistent with BuildingConnected policies.

## Cookies

We may collect non-identifiable information from visitors to our Site through the use of cookies and other technologies. A cookie is a piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer but not you. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some of our websites may not work properly.

## Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and to use correctly the information we collect online.

## Access and Correction of Personal Information

You will be able to access and update the personal information that you provided when registering your account on the Site. If you wish to obtain a copy of particular information you provided to BuildingConnected, or if you become aware the information is incorrect and you would like us to correct it, contact us at privacy@BuildingConnected.com.

## Notification of Changes

We reserve the right to amend this Policy at any time. A notice will be posted on the homepage of the Site for 30 days whenever this Policy is changed in a material way. Your use of the Site or Services after the notice is posted constitute your acceptance of such changes. Your sole and exclusive remedy if you do not agree with such changes is to cease your use of the Site and the Services.

## Privacy Questions and Access

If you have a question about this Policy, you can send an email to the BuildingConnected at info@BuildingConnected.com. You can also contact us at this address if you have a question about BuildingConnected's handling of your information.

If you wish to obtain a copy of particular information you provided to BuildingConnected, or if you become aware the information is incorrect and you would like us to correct it contact us at info@BuildingConnected.com.

## Your California Privacy Rights 

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information to third parties for those third parties' direct marketing purposes. California residents can make such a request by writing to us at the following address: 156 2nd Street, San Francisco, CA 94105

Effective as of September 13, 2017.
